WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
Yes
or
No!
Tsunade's
Answer
Not good...
Damn it! Damn it!
This time for sure... no matter what!
You're the only one who can treat
Orochimaru-sama's arms.
Why don't we make a deal?
I'll resurrect the little brother
and man, both of whom you loved...
with the Forbidden Jutsu I've developed.
Don't you want to see those two,
Tsunade...?
No! You must not believe
in their sweet talk...
Their wishes...
Moreover, Tsunade-sama, your wishes...
And dreams...
Did you forget them?!
I'll be straight with you.
Tsunade, the village has demanded
that you become the Fifth Hokage.
The successive line of Hokages
have protected the Leaf Village
and those living in it.
They brought troubled times under control
and helped the village to prosper.
They risked their lives for
this dream, this ideal!
You don't have to answer right now.
However, I want it in a week.
Also, two human sacrifices are
needed for this Forbidden Jutsu,
so do what you need to do
to prepare them.
We are starting!
C'mon. Place your bets!
Which will you bet on, ma'am?
Which one? C'mon!
Which one will she choose?
If she agrees to our conditions,
your arms will be healed,
and the destruction of the Leaf Village
will continue immediately.
Tsunade-sama will also be able to
be reunited with the two whom she loves.
But if she doesn't agree...
I'll have to force her to heal my arms...
Will it really be that easy?
I have you.
There's no need to worry.
I'm the one who knows her the best.
And her greatest weakness!
She'll definitely accept the conditions...
Definitely!
Listen, in this third step,
you've got to use 100%
of what you have learned...
And retain them.
In other words,
imagine creating a single layer
within the balloon
and compressing the Chakra inside it.
I know that in my head...
But no matter what,
I can't completely hold 100%
of my power in a neat ball...
Don't give him false hope by teaching him
something he can't master.
That's why the oblivious kid
starts joking about becoming a Hokage!
Tomorrow, huh.
Come again, okay?
I certainly will!
Are you going to meet
Orochimaru again?
To think she'd be that shaken up...
Something extreme must have happened.
That one week bugs me, somehow...
And Naruto hasn't come back
to the inn for nearly a week.
I guess I'll press Tsunade a little more.
No good...
No good... Why?
Here there's no time...
It'll be too late.
What's this...?!
What happened, Naruto-kun?!
Are you okay?
What do you want?
The moon's out.
How about going out for a drink?
Tomorrow will be the one week
you promised to Naruto.
I wonder what became of Naruto?
Beats me.
I guess I'll have something.
Radish, please.
Coming up.
Oh?
Here you go.
Ooh! This looks good.
Tsunade-sama!
What happened to Naruto-kun?
He's quite exhausted and weakened.
And his right hand is severely burned
with Chakra...
As it stands now,
this kid probably won't wake up
until the day after tomorrow.
It's as Jiraiya says...
Why did I make such a stupid bet?
What am I, of all people,
getting so worked up for?
How stupid.
Tomorrow...
Please don't go tomorrow!
Why don't you say anything?!
Tsunade-sama! Please don't be silent.
Please answer!
If you say that you're going...
What will you do?
I'll stop you with my life!
Shizune... Have you forgotten
who you're talking to?
Sir! It's morning, now!
It's about time you went home!
Jeez.
Hey! Get up, sir...
Hey! What's wrong, you?!
It'll be troublesome if we're disturbed
during the negotiations...
What do you want me to do?
It might be good to kill...
Tsunade's attendant.
It seems that you...
You don't trust me completely... yet.
Precisely because I trust you...
I would like to leave Sasuke-kun
in your hands.
Well, then...
Kabuto...
If you wish to stop me...
You have no choice
but to kill young Sasuke-kun, now.
You can't possibly kill me...
Hey!
I said hey!
Naruto-kun...?
Oh no! What time is it?
No, what day is it?
It's Monday...
What is it?
Is your body okay?
As I recall, you were supposed
to sleep for two full days...
No matter what the wound,
I'm always able to recover
if I sleep one night!
That's right.
This kid has Nine-Tailed Fox's power...
More importantly,
where's that stupid old woman?!
Today's the promised bet day.
Then, what about the Jutsu...
It's still not complete, but I can wing it...
That's right. This isn't the time for this.
— Naruto-kun, please stay...
— Huh?
You are...!
What?! Oh!
Wait, Shizune!
That damned Tsunade spiked my drink.
I can't build up my Chakra well...
And my body is so numb,
I can barely throw a Kunai Knife.
What was he gonna do
if that had hit me?!
That's lame! Here you're always bragging
about how you're this awesome Ninja!
And you're nailed by her perverted attack?
You, Pervy Pervy Sage?!
Shut up!
Even if she's rotten,
she's still a medical specialist.
She's the only one who could concoct
a tasteless and odorless drug for Ninja.
But to think I'd be caught off-guard,
no matter how intoxicated I was...
I'm going to kill you, bastard!
How are you feeling,
Jiraiya-sama?
Quite a bit better than this morning I
guess.
But be that as it may,
maybe around thirty percent...
I never thought I'd end up encountering
that Jiraiya-sama in a place like this...
Things have gotten difficult.
I guess I'll pull back for now.
At any rate, Naruto-kun...
To think you'd be here, too...
Hey! Shizune.
Y-Yes?!
It's about time you tell me
what the hell she was talking about
with Orochimaru.
Orochimaru?!
I wanted to believe Tsunade-sama...
That's why I couldn't say until now.
But...
There's no time.
Please come with me!
I'll explain as we run!
Okay!
I'm going, too!
What's your answer?
Say what?!
The answer to that is definitely no!
This might be really bad...
She's probably still thinking
of those two.
Perhaps I may have no choice,
but to kill Tsunade...
Damn it!
I'll heal your arms...
In exchange for that,
keep your hands off the village.
Very well.
Now then...
He's planning to once again attack
the Leaf Village if
his arms are healed!
The situation will get
even more dangerous than that
if he's not stopped now.
Him screwing around like that!
I have you.
There's no need to worry...
What's the meaning of this?
To think you'd betray me at this point...
Tsunade!
I BELIEVE YOUR PROMISE ITS TRUE HEART TO GIVE ME COURAGE
I believe your promise, it's a true heart gives me courage
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
tachidomatta kado ni
on your still shoulder
asu e mukau kaze wo kanjiteta
I feel the wind that blows towards tomorrow
machi no akari hoshikuzu mitai ni
the city lights are like pieces of stars
futari tsutsumu kedo
that hold us together
sorezore ni chigau kagayaki ga aru to
"each one of us glows differently"
warau kimi ga
you say laughingly
ichiban mabushiku mieru yo
but you look most dazzling
yume wa ryuusei no you ni
like a comet
ameagari no niji no you ni
like the rainbow after the storm
kono kokoro ni hikari wo tsuretekuru
you bring light into my heart
nayami tsuzukeru koto ga hitotsu no kotae ni naruyo
being lost can be the answer
gomakashitari shinai to chikau no
let's promise we won't cheat
ALWAYS I FEEL IT THE PRECIOUS TIME WITH YOU
always I feel it the precious time with you
What the hell is this?! This castle
has been destroyed even further!
It seems Tsunade has
declined the deal.
But... but the old lady is not here!
Calm down a second.
She shouldn't have gone far from here.
Oh, some incredible noise
from that direction, Pervy Sage!
Well, well... she started a flashy battle.
Naruto, we go after her!
Right! I'm ready anytime!
Next time:
"Negotiations Broken Down!!"